Schauntice Marie Marshall 20 Green Street - Windsor, CT 06095 860-938-2662

Email: sschauntice@yahoo.com schaunticemarshall@gmail.com

Summary of Qualifications:

Over Five Years of Customer Service Experience

Proven ability to meet or exceed Customer Service oriented goals

Ability to communicate professionally through written and verbal skills

Ability to maintain and strengthen relationships with existing and prospective clients and internal staff/teammates

Pleasant Personality, hard working, and dedicated to the improvement of Customer Service

Education:

University of Hartford – Hartt School of Music

Graduate Professional Diploma

2011- Present

Shenandoah University-Conservatory:

Bachelor of Vocal Performance (Opera Concentration)

1998 - 2003

Professional Experience:

International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Wash., D.C.

March 2007 - December 2009

Administrative Assistant – Council on Industrial Relations

Serving as an office information manager and liaison for the director of the arbitration department, arranging and scheduling meetings or appointments, organizing and preserving paper and computer files, managing projects, handling travel arrangements, performing research, and distributing information through the use of telephones, mail, and e-mail. Responsible for organizing and updating union bylaws across the US and Canada, training support secretary, and documenting and organizing departmental handbook.

Data Control Clerk – Reciprocity Department

Coordinate and expedite the flow of materials within the department to establish a production schedule. Duties include reviewing and distributing work, and conferring with department supervisors to determine progress of work and completion dates; and relaying the information to the client. Examining documents and supporting materials in order to assess completeness, accuracy, and conformance to process benefit payments

Kastle Systems, Arlington, VA

March 2004 – February 2007

Account Executive

To be the liaison and lead contact for high profile portfolio clients through consistent communication via telephone, and on-site visits on a regular basis, and to maintain an excellent rapport with the clients, evaluate prospective and existing customers' security needs and generate proposals to meet those needs, Coordinate system installation with the customer and the appropriate Kastle departments, Conduct instructional briefings and provide system documentation to the client and their staff, Soliciting feedback regarding the operational effectiveness of services and the system, coordinating in-house personnel as necessary to resolve problems, Update and maintain a standard letters and proposal guide, Review proposals, installation work orders, correspondence and billing adjustments for accuracy before submittal to the Manager, Examine weekly installation schedule.

Customer Service Account Manager

Daily duties: Card administration, suite system notifications, response to incoming emails and phone calls, respond to pricing inquiries in an accurate and timely fashion, providing training support to new employees, initiate and conduct security system consultations and evaluate the needs of the client, perform calculations of credit adjustments and forward adjustments accordingly, provide tenant sales and co-ordinate the installation of suite systems accordingly, and assist customers in daily task, trouble shooting, training oncoming team members and staff.

Grafton School, Berryville, VA

August 2000 - September 2004

Special Needs Home Assistant

Daily duties: Notation of daily activities for clientele, medication administration logs, provide detailed information to the guardian for the assisted clientele, assist clientele with daily living skills and motivational skills, provide alternative outlets for daily activities, work closely with staff to ensure safety of clientele, and clienteles personal information, transition from home environment to functional work environment for clientele

Additional Skills: Knowledge of Windows 98/2000, Excel, Word, Microsoft Office